





## **Important**

 Using Free CV Search you have access to featured candidate profiles of Naukri. You can browse through the profiles and email the candidates of your choice directly using the email option provided. To prevent misuse of candidate information, contact details and attached resume of the candidates have been withheld

# Summary

Jump to Section

Last Active: 21-Jan-21

Certified Business Analyst having 5+ years of experience in Finance domain

Adynamic professional, holding an MB.Adegree in Finance

Highly Effective in analysing and interpreting financial data to achieve desired outcomes.

Last Modified: 20-Jan-21

Work Experience | Education | IT Skills |

Result-oriented and driven to excel at each and every task.

Highly organized for multitasking while maintaining high quality of work.

Ability to produce desirable results with minimal or zero supervision.

Exceptional analytical and problem solving skills.

Verified : Phone Number | Email - id

Excellent team worker with solid leadership and management skills.

## **Work Experience**

Edelweiss Financial Services as Assistant Manager - IT May 2018 to Till Date

Responsibilities

Understanding the detailed business of Edelweiss Alternative Asset Advisors from business team.

Understanding the detailed process of various Debt Strategies like Real Estate, Stressed Asset, and Infrastructure etc.

Understanding the different fund structure from various stakeholders.

Understanding and implementing various Fund Investment structure in FIT (Financial Info Through Tech) application. Analysing and Designing complete fund structure and providing end to end solution to Front and Mddle office team. Customizing the modular and flexible framework to various stakeholders.

Identifying and analysing day to day activities performed by Risk/Compliance, product, FINOPS and Deal team. Understanding of complete Fund Investments and Portfolio Investment structure from Front and Mddle office team.

Analysing different deal structure and Investor management process from the business team.

Identifying and analysing Reports and Analytics of various modules for various stakeholders.

Prepared Business Requirement Document (BRD), Functional Specification Document (FSD) and Test Case Document for FIT applications.

Performed UAT testing of all the modules and resolving defects and provide solutions.

Responsible for creating User Authorization Matrix and providing training to business users.

Client Name: DARB (Distressed Asset Resolution Business) Project Name: ARC (Asset Reconstruction Company)

Capgemini as Process Associate Aug 2016 to Jan 2018

Responsibilities:

Reference Data Management process for Euro bonds.

Understanding the detailed flow of Work Fusion activity from business team.

Gather high level requirements from Business team and develop the BRD document as per the requirement. Gathered low level requirements from Users who have all necessary information or records i.e., subject matter expert to Prepare FRD (Functional Requirement Document).

Gathered detailed flow of requirements to be processed and captured in to the system.

Identifying the type of instruments and documents provided by the team meets the requirement of the process. Ensured only the supported type is uploaded and mapped into the system and the output file generated of all the

data mapped in to the system, matches the data provided.

Prepared Business Requirements Document (BRD), Functional Specification Document (FSD) and Non-Functional Document and prepared Test Case Document for Work Fusion Application.

Supported as well as coordinated User Acceptance Testing (UAT) for production defects.

Fair understanding and interpreting financial reports Term Sheets, Clear stream, Euro clear, Prospectus, Base Prospectus for determining the financial data of various Issuers.

Managing Client Requests, Queries, Work Allocation and analysing Risk involved in the financial products.

Analysing new financial securities in the market and Coding and Listing of securities in the market

Executing Data Analysis from different sources and understanding Investment logics and Pricing of various sources.

Responsible for setting up ISIN and creation of Valoren number for each source

Responsible for Training and Monitoring team members for creation and coding of various Financial Securities.

Performing Work Fusion activity and assisting Automation team for building Macros.

#### eClerx Services (P) Ltd as Analyst

May 2015 to Aug 2016

Responsibilities:

Fixed Income products trade reconciliation for Corporate / Municipal / Treasury bonds.

Working as a bridge to find out issues related to Unmatched/Unsettled trades (bonds products) and how to fix them.

Trade confirmation over phone/Email with contra brokers.

Finding out discrepancies in trades done with counter parties and reaching out to concerned trading desk to get these discrepancies resolved.

Ensure timely settlements for over 50 markets worldwide.

Performing calculations on Bloomberg for accurate figures related to coupon and interest.

Trade amendments and preparing price variance report for trade support group.

Escalate unresolved discrepancies to management.

Monitor and correct institutional accounts

Manage and reduce risk associated with settlement failure.

Train team members on Bloomberg, Euro clear and clear stream systems.

^ Back to Top

#### **Education**

UG: B.Sc (Computers) from Mumbai University in 2012

PG: MBA/PGDM (Finance) from Mumbai University in 2015

^ Back to Top

#### IT Skills

Skill Name	Version Last Used Experience
Microsoft Visio	
indigo studio	

^ Back to Top

### Languages Known

Language	Proficiency	Read	Write	Speak
English				
Hindi				
Marathi				
Gujarati				

^ Back to Top

#### **Affirmative Action**

#### **Work Authorization**

Category: General Physically Challenged: No Job Type: Permanent Employment Status: Full time

^ Back to Top

Careers - About Us - Clients - Terms & Conditions - FAQ's - Contact Us - Report a Problem - Site Map - Resources Our Partners: Jeevansathi Matrimonials - ICIClcommunities.org - 99acres - Real Estate In India All rights reserved © 2021 Info Edge India Ltd.

All rights reserved © 2021 Info Edge India Ltd.